<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on BlueSam1905</title>
    <link>https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on BlueSam1905</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Dangers of Public WiFi- A Cyber Security Specialist&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/publicwifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/publicwifi/</guid>
      <description>Initialization Everywhere offers free WiFi. It&amp;rsquo;s alluring to connect to free WiFi networks to reduce your data usage, whether you&amp;rsquo;re in a coffee shop, airport, or hotel. But as an expert in cyber security, I strongly advise against using open WiFi. This blog post will outline the dangers of using public WiFi and provide safety advice.
Connections That Are Not Encrypted Since public WiFi networks frequently lack encryption, anyone can eavesdrop on the information you send and receive over the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Open Source Software and Why Should You Care?</title>
      <link>https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/opensource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bluesam1905.github.io/articles/opensource/</guid>
      <description>Initialization Open source software is a category of software that is freely usable, modifiable, and distributable by anyone. We will define open source software and discuss its significance in this blog post.
Teamwork and Knowledge Exchange Developer collaboration and knowledge sharing are encouraged by open source software. The software&amp;rsquo;s source code can be made available to everyone so that programmers can learn from one another&amp;rsquo;s experience and insights. Together, programmers can create software that is more dependable, secure, and stable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
